# NAHEEN HABIB

# Front End Developer

## CONTACT

0405 277 473

naheenhabib36@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/naheen-habib

### SKILLS

HTML

**CSS** 

UX/UI Design

JavaScript

**REACT** 

GIT

Amazon Web Services

Cloud Integration

Search Engine Optimisation

Computer Networking

PHP

Web Development

Software Development

CI/CD

Video Editing

Photoshop

Adobe Premier Pro

Figma

Fetching APIs

## REFERENCES

Provided upon request

## SUMMARY

A cyber security student with volunteer and workplace experience in software development and front end development. Practised in HTML, CSS and JavaScript with experience using REACT software. Keen to further develop professional skills and advance in the field of Cyber Security.

## EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF CYBER SECURITY AND BEHAVIOUR

Western Sydney University

March 2021 - Present

#### CCNA INTRODUCTION TO NETWORKS

Cisco

Jan 2022

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## CYBER SECURITY SPECIALIST

Moodchart.ai - Sydney NSW

March 2023 - Present

- Advising on Cyber Security Compliance
- Reviewing Privacy and Security Laws
- Project Management/Collaboration with Colleagues
- Front-End Development
- Penetration Testing for Vulnerabilities

#### **VOLUNTEER DEVELOPER**

Code.Sydney - Sydney NSW

May 2022 - Present

- Assisting with Development for Lloyd Consulting Using JS React and SCSS (Portfolio-like Site for a Consultant and Advocate in Criminal Justice)
- Assisting with Project Development